http://www.hoenle.com/privacy-policy

Data privacy policy
Thank you for your interest in our company. In the following, we are pleased to provide you with information regarding the processing of personal data when using this website at hoenle.de in accordance with Article 13 EU General Data Protection Regulation (EU GDPR).
The controller of this website in the sense of the EU GDPR and other national data protection laws of the member states and other data protection regulations is:
Dr. Hönle AG
Lochhamer Schlag 1
82166 Gräfelfing
Telephone: +49 (0) 89 856 08 - 0
Fax: +49 (0) 89 856 08 - 148
Email: uv@hoenle.de
The controller’s data protection officer is
Dr Karsten Kinast, lawyer, LL.M.
KINAST Rechtsanwaltsgesellschaft mbH
Hohenzollernring 54
50672 Cologne
Tel.: +49 (0)221 – 222 183 – 0
Email: mail@kinast.eu
Website: https://www.kinast.eu
I. General information about data processing
We only process our users’ personal data if this is necessary to provide a functioning website as well as our contents and services.
If we obtain the consent of the data subject for processing personal data, Article 6 Para. 1 Lit. a EU GDPR serves as the legal basis.
When processing personal data required for the performance of a contract to which the data subject is a party, Article 6 Para. 1 Lit. b EU GDPR serves as the legal basis. This also applies to processing required for executing precontractual measures.
If processing personal data is required to fulfil a legal obligation to which our company is subject, Article 6 Para. 1 Lit. c EU GDPR serves as the legal basis.
In the event that the vital interests of the data subject or another natural person make processing personal data necessary, Article 6 Para. 1 Lit. d EU GDPR serves as the legal basis.
If processing is necessary to safeguard a legitimate interest of our company or a third party and if the interests, fundamental rights and freedoms of the data subject do not outweigh the first-mentioned interest, Article 6 Para. 1 Lit. f EU GDPR serves as the legal basis for processing.
The personal data of the data subject is deleted or blocked as soon as the purpose for storage ceases to exist. Furthermore, data may be stored if this has been provided for by the European or national legislator in EU regulations, laws or other provisions to which the controller is subject. The data will also be blocked or deleted if a storage period prescribed by the aforementioned standards expires unless there is a need for further storage of the data for the conclusion or fulfilment of a contract.
We sometimes use specialised providers (e.g. for hosting the pages or sending newsletters) to provide our website or for certain services on the website. These providers operate as service providers for us and may also obtain knowledge of your personal data in connection with the maintenance and servicing of the systems. We have concluded “data processing contracts” with these providers in accordance with Article 28 EU GDPR, which ensure that data processing is carried out in a permissible manner.
II. Provision of the website and creation of log files
On every visit to our website, our system automatically collects data and information from the computer system of the computer being used.
The following data is collected:
(1) information about the browser type, including the version and language used
(2) the user’s operating system, including interface
(3) the user’s IP address
(4) date and time of access
(5) page of origin (HTTP-referrer)
(6) accessed address (2nd-level-domain.1st-level-domain/accessed_page)
(7) call status/HTTP status code
(8) amount of data transferred
The data is also stored in the log files of our system. Storage of this data together with other personal data of the user does not take place.
The legal basis for the temporary storage of the data and log files is Article 6 Para. 1 Lit. f EU GDPR.
The temporary storage of the IP address by the system is necessary to enable delivery of the website to the user’s computer. The user’s IP address must be stored for the duration of the session for this purpose.
Data is stored in log files to ensure the functionality of the website. The data also helps us to optimise the website and to ensure the security of our information technology systems. An analysis of the data for marketing purposes does not take place in this context.
Our legitimate interest in data processing in accordance with Article 6 Para. 1 Lit. f EU GDPR also lies in these purposes.
The data is deleted as soon as it is no longer necessary for achieving the purpose of its collection. In the case of data collection for the provision of the website, this is the case when the respective session has ended.
In the case of data being stored in log files, this is the case after seven days at the latest. Further storage is possible. Users’ IP addresses are distorted after just two days at the latest so that assignment to the visiting client is no longer possible.
The collection of the data for website provision and data storage in log files is necessary for operating the website. As a result, there is no objection option for the user.
III. Use of cookies
Our website uses cookies. Cookies are text files that are stored in the Internet browser or by the Internet browser of the user’s computer system. If a user visits a website, a cookie may be stored on the user’s operating system. This cookie contains a characteristic string that enables the unique identification of the browser when the website is visited again.
We use cookies to make our website more user-friendly. These are exclusively “session cookies”, which are deleted after leaving the website.
The purpose of using technically necessary cookies is to simplify the use of websites for users. Some functions on our website cannot be offered without using cookies. For this it is necessary that the browser is recognised even after a page change.
The following data is stored and transmitted in the cookies:
(1) language settings
(2) pages visited
The legal basis for processing personal data using cookies is Article 6 Para. 1 Lit. f. EU GDPR.
We require cookies for the following applications:
(1) acceptance of language settings
(2) user frequency of pages
The user data collected by technically necessary cookies is not used to create user profiles.
Our legitimate interest in processing personal data in accordance with Article 6 Para. 1 Lit. f EU GDPR also lies in these purposes.
Cookies are stored on the user’s computer and transmitted to our site. Therefore, you as the user also have full control over the use of cookies. You can deactivate or restrict the transmission of cookies by changing the settings in your Internet browser. Cookies that are already stored can be deleted at any time. This can be done automatically. If cookies are deactivated for our website, it is possible that not all functions can be used to their full extent.
IV. Display and use of third-party content
Our website uses “Content Delivery Networks” (CDN) as well as other tools from third-party providers. CDN ensure that the loading time of common JavaScript libraries and fonts are reduced because the files are transferred from fast, nearby or underused servers. In addition, we use Google Maps to visually display geographical information.
The legal basis for processing personal data using CDN and other tools is Article 6 Para. 1 Lit. f. EU GDPR.
We use the following third-party providers:
• Google Inc. for the use of “Google Fonts” and “Google Maps”
When using CDN and other tools, your IP address, among other things, is transmitted to the third-party providers. Even though the third-party providers operate servers in the EU, it cannot be excluded that your browser also accesses servers outside the EU. For more detailed information about which personal data are processed by Google, Inc. in this relation, see https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en&gl=de
The use of CDN and other tools is in the interest of presenting our website in a uniform and appealing way. Our legitimate interest in processing personal data in accordance with Article 6 Para. 1 Lit. f EU GDPR also lies in these purposes.
You can generally deactivate the execution of JavaScript by changing the settings in your Internet browser. If JavaScript is deactivated for our website, it is possible that not all functions can be used to their full extent.
V. Use of Google Analytics
We use tracking and analysis tools to ensure that our website is continuously optimised and appropriately designed. Tracking also makes it possible for us to statistically record the use of our website by visitors and to further develop our website for you with the help of knowledge gained from this. These interests justify the use of the tracking and analysis tools described below in accordance with Article 6 Para. 1 Sentence 1 Lit. f GDPR. If you have given us your consent to the use of cookies based on a notice (“cookie banner”) that we issued on the website, the legality of the use is additionally in accordance with Article 6 Para. 1 Sentence 1 Lit. a GDPR. The following description of tracking and analysis tools also indicates the respective processing purposes and processed data.
This website uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google Inc. ("Google"). Google Analytics uses "cookies", which are text files placed on your computer to help the website analyse how visitors use the site. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the website will normally be transmitted to and stored by Google on a server in the USA. This means that the IP is only stored anonymously, meaning your IP address will be truncated beforehand within a member state of the European Union or in other contracting states to the agreement on the European Economic Area. Only in exceptional cases will the full IP address be transmitted to a Google server in the United States and truncated there. Google will use this information for the purpose of evaluating your use of the website, compiling reports on website activity for website operators and providing other services relating to website activity and internet usage. Google will not associate your IP address transferred within the framework of Google Analytics with any other data held by Google. You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser, however, please note that if you do this you may not be able to use the full functionality of this website. Furthermore, you can prevent Google’s collection and use of data generated by the cookie and related to your use of the website (including your IP address) by downloading and installing the browser plug-in or alternatively clicking on the following link to opt out of cookies (https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en).
In addition or as an alternative to the browser add-on, you can prevent tracking by Google Analytics on our pages by clicking on this link: Deactivate Google Analytics. This installs an opt-out cookie on your device. This will prevent Google Analytics from collecting data for this website and for this browser in the future as long as the cookie remains installed in your browser.
Further information and the applicable Google privacy policy can be found at https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en&gl=de and http://www.google.com/analytics/terms/de.html. Google Analytics is explained in more detail using this link https://marketingplatform.google.com/intl/en_uk/about/.
VI. Newsletter
There is the option of subscribing to a free newsletter on our website.
Your consent is obtained for data processing and reference is made to this data privacy policy during the registration process. The data is only used for sending the newsletter.
The legal basis for processing the data after the user has registered for the newsletter is Article 6 Para. 1 Lit. a EU GDPR if the user has given consent.
The data is deleted as soon as it is no longer necessary for achieving the purpose of its collection. The user’s data will therefore be stored as long as the newsletter subscription is active.
The newsletter subscription can be cancelled by the user concerned at any time. There is a corresponding link in each newsletter for this purpose.
VII. Contact forms and email contact
There are contact forms on our website that can be used for electronic contact. If a user uses this option, the data entered in the input screen will be transmitted to us and stored.
Alternatively, you can contact us via the email address(es) provided. In this case, the user’s personal data transmitted by email will be stored.
The legal basis for processing data transferred as part of using the contact form or sending an email is Article 6 Para. 1 Lit. f. EU GDPR.
If the use of the contact form or the transmission of an email serves to fulfil a contract to which the user is a party or to execute pre-contractual measures, the legal basis for processing the data is Article 6 Para. 1 Lit. b GDPR.
Processing personal data from the input screen or in the event of contact being made by email is solely for the purpose of facilitating contact with us.
Our legitimate interest in processing personal data in accordance with Article 6 Para. 1 Lit. f EU GDPR also lies in these purposes if it does not already involve the fulfilment of a contract to which the user is a party or the execution of pre-contractual measures.
The data is deleted as soon as it is no longer necessary for achieving the purpose of its collection. For personal data from the contact form input screen and that which was sent by email, this is the case when the respective conversation with the user is finished. The conversation is terminated when the circumstances show that it is certain that the matter in question has been conclusively resolved. If there are legal storage periods for the communication content, e.g. due to commercial and/or tax law provisions, the corresponding data will be deleted after these periods have expired.
If there are no legal storage obligations, the user can object to the storage of their personal data at any time. In a case such as this, the conversation cannot be continued.
All personal data stored in the course of contacting us will be deleted in this case.
VIII. Rights of the data subject
You as data subject have the right to information according to Article 15 GDPR, the right to correction according to Article 16 GDPR, the right to deletion according to Article 17 GDPR, the right to restrict processing according to Article 18 GDPR, the right to objection from Article 21 GDPR and the right to data transferability from Article 20 GDPR. With regard to the right to information and the right to deletion, the restrictions in accordance with Sections 34 and 35 Federal Data Protection Act – BDSG – (new) shall apply. Furthermore, you have the right to complain to a data protection supervisory authority (Article 77 EU GDPR in conjunction with Section 19 BDSG (new)). The supervisory authority responsible for us is the Bavarian State Office for Data Privacy Supervision (Bayerisches Landesamt für Datenschutzaufsicht), PO box 606, 91511 Ansbach.
You can revoke your consent to the processing of personal data at any time. This also applies to the revocation of declarations of consent that were issued to us before the EU GDPR came into force, therefore, before 25 May 2018. Please note that the revocation will only take effect in the future. Processing that took place prior to revocation is not affected by this.
Cookie Notice
Company
Our Profile
Corporate History
The Hönle Group
Trade Fairs & Seminars
Locations
Corporate History
Solar Simulation (SoSi)
Solar Simulation (SoSi)
